yogiproducts.com 2012-12-25

# Yogi - Privacy Policy

Yogi is committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors to our Web site. The following policy describes how we collect, protect and use information we receive. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy statement, our use of your information, or if you would like to change how we communicate with you, please [email us](mailto:YogiTea.CustomerService@yogiproducts.com).

**What information does Yogi collect and how does Yogi use it?**

Yogi collects several types of information on our Web site. We collect personal information based on information that you provide when you request to receive email, newsletters or other products or services from Yogi. We use this information to ensure you receive the correct products and services via email in a timely manner. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer any of your information to outside parties.

When registering, you will have the option to sign up for our mailing list. You may elect to opt-out of correspondence from Yogi at any time.

We may also use the information we collect during the registration process to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the website, new products and services and special offers we think you'd enjoy. If you prefer to not receive this information, or would like to opt-out of any other communication, simply use the unsubscribe link provided in the email.

**How does Yogi protect visitor information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information that includes saving your personal information on a secured network with limited access. This information is required by Yogi to be kept confidential.

**What are "cookies"? Does Yogi use "cookies"?**

Yogi uses cookies: small text files that are stored on your computer by a Web server based on permissions set in your browser software. Cookies do not read any information on your personal computer, rather, they're used as identifiers by our Web site to customize, monitor, or regulate the use of the Yogi site based on information stored on the host server. The use of cookies is commonplace and standard Internet practice.

Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you may be able customize your browser options to prevent and/or notify you when you are sent a cookie. The notification option allows you to decide whether or not you would like to accept the cookie. Not accepting cookies from our Web site still enable you to access and use site features.

**A note to parents:**

Our site is a general audience site that is neither designed nor intended to collect personal information from children. Yogi cares about the safety and privacy of children online and complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulation establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. Children under the age of 13 should not provide any personal information on the site. We ask that parents supervise their children while online.

In the case that Yogi receives information pertaining to persons under 13, we will immediately obtain parental consent or delete the information from our servers. If you want to notify us of our potential receipt of information by children under 13, please [email us](mailto:YogiTea.CustomerService@yogiproducts.com).

**Third party links:**

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. However, even if the third party is affiliated with Yogi, we have no control over these linked sites. Each of these sites has their own separate and independent privacy, data collection policies and practices. Yogi is not responsible or liable for the content of these linked sites, as they are provided for your convenience and are to be accessed at your own risk. We do, however, seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about external links, including information regarding a broken link.

**Your consent:**

By using the Yogi Web site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy:**

We will change, amend and update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our privacy practices, technology, products and services, general business operations and industry. In the event of any such change, we will post a revised policy on this Web site and revise the "Last Updated" date of such policy. We reserve the right to change, amend and update this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole and absolute discretion, and such changes will be effective upon posting of the revised policy. In the event of a material change in our information collection and use practices, we will provide more prominent notice of such change along with the revision to the effective date of the policy. You should check this Privacy Policy on a regular basis to ensure you have reviewed and are familiar with the most current policy.

**Contacting Us**

For any questions or concerns you may have regarding this Privacy Policy and our information and data collection and use practices, please contact us at:

VIA MAIL: 950 International Way  
Springfield, Oregon 97477

VIA EMAIL: [YogiTea.CustomerService@yogiproducts.com](mailto:YogiTea.CustomerService@yogiproducts.com)

Last revised: July 26, 2012
